<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Upsella Website Design</title><link>https://www.upsella.org/</link><description>Recent content on Upsella Website Design</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2022 04:20:46 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.upsella.org/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Big goals for small business websites.</title><link>https://www.upsella.org/blog/2022/12/16/big-goals-for-websites/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2022 04:20:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.upsella.org/blog/2022/12/16/big-goals-for-websites/</guid><description>To ensure that your website is low maintenance, cost-effective, and flexible, it&amp;rsquo;s important to choose the right technology and implementation partner. Upsella provides a full range of services for getting up and running with a modern business website.</description></item><item><title>About Upsella</title><link>https://www.upsella.org/about-us/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.upsella.org/about-us/</guid><description>1. Our Business UpSella is a web design agency that was created by professionals who have a passion for internet marketing, creative design and website building. Our mission is to help small businesses and non-profits to increase sales with online marketing. Your website is the gold standard for online home base. We will help you to create a site that accurately establishes your business and brand image, and if needed with ability to accept payments online.</description></item><item><title>Contact</title><link>https://www.upsella.org/contact/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.upsella.org/contact/</guid><description>Contact Us Are you curious about something? Do you have an issue with your Website? Would you want to order a website or request online marketing? Please let us know, we are here to help you and will get back to you right away.</description></item><item><title>Portfolio</title><link>https://www.upsella.org/portfolio/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.upsella.org/portfolio/</guid><description>Our Portfolio Businesses like E39source, WizLegal, and more have trusted us to build their websites. Check out our case studies and projects below.
  e39source - E39 BMW repair shop and a comprehensive resource for BMW E39 enthusiasts, offering technical information, guides, and community support. WizLegal - An AI Legal Assistant platform, providing intelligent solutions for legal professionals and real estate agents.</description></item><item><title>Terms and Conditions</title><link>https://www.upsella.org/terms-and-conditions/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.upsella.org/terms-and-conditions/</guid><description>MASTER SERVICE AGREEMENT Last Updated: December 08, 2022
This MSA is made and entered into by and between the individual or entity executing this MSA as the customer (“Customer”, “You”) and UpSella, LLC. (“Company”, “Provider”). For purposes of this MSA, Customer and Company shall be referred to collectively as the “Parties” and each individually as a “Party.”
WHEREAS, Company provides Website Hosting Services, domain registration, SEO optimization, and website development services.</description></item><item><title>Thank you</title><link>https://www.upsella.org/thank-you/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.upsella.org/thank-you/</guid><description>window.dataLayer = window.dataLayer || []; function gtag(){dataLayer.push(arguments);} gtag('js', new Date()); gtag('config', 'UA-251685014-1'); Thank you for your purchase. One of our representatives will contact you to discuss the implementation.
Please provide additional details if you prefer to setup a Zoom meeting or phone call.</description></item><item><title>UpSella Pricing</title><link>https://www.upsella.org/pricing/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.upsella.org/pricing/</guid><description>Website Design Services - Initial Implementation We build your business website for as little as $900. We use open source technology to run your site at minimum cost while providing high reliability. We offer small, medium, large, or custom websites based on your needs. Please select one of the initial implementation packages below.
Email us at contact@UpSella.org if you prefer a custom payment plan (invoice billing) or custom requirements for your website.</description></item></channel></rss>